Fairy Tales Do Come True
A Prince for Christmas is a romance, tv movie film directed by Fred Olen Ray.
A prince from Europe meets a charming waitress when he travels to America
during the Christmas holiday to escape an arranged marriage.
Emma, played by Viva Bianca.
Prince Duncan, played by Kirk Barker.
Todd, played by Aaron O'Connell.
Alice, played by Brittany Beery.
Queen Ariana, played by Kelly LeBrock.
King, played by Maxwell Caulfield.
A Prince for Christmas is a 2015 American made-for-television Christmas romantic drama film produced
and directed by Fred Olen Ray and starring Viva Bianca, Kirk Barker and Aaron O'Connell.
The film was originally called Small Town Prince and
premiered on Starz network on November 29, 2015.
The film explores themes of prince, royalty, christmas.
The tone is emotional.